Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2014
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in rehearsal with Norrbotten NEO members: flutist Sara Hammarström and violoncellist Elemér Lavotha at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6929June in Buffalo.tif (Image-file jib2014_070)
- Composer Hilda Paredes in rehearsal with pianist Märten Landström of Norrbotten NEO at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6930Hilda Paredes.tif (Image-file jib2014_071)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg in rehearsal with conductor Petter Sundkvist, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, and flutist Sara Hammarström at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6933composer Fineberg and Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_072)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6937Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_073)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6938Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_074)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6938Irving Arditti=.tif (Image-file jib2014_075)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6940Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_076)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6943Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_077)
- Pianist Märten Landström in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6945Norbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_078)
- Pianist Märten Landström rehearsing on a flexatone at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6953June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_079)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6966Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_080)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist onstage after a performance with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violist Kim Hellgren, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, percussionist Daniel Saur, flutist Sara Hammarström, and clarinetist Robert Ek at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6968 Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_081)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violist Kim Hellgren, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, percussionist Daniel Saur, flutist Sara Hammarström, and clarinetist Robert Ek at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6970Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_082)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with Norrbotten NEO members: flutist Sara Hammarström, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, and clarinetist Robert Ek at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6974Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_083)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with Norrbotten NEO members: flutist Sara Hammarström, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, and clarinetist Robert Ek at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6975June in Buffalo Norrbotten Neo.tif (Image-file jib2014_084)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, clarinetist Robert Ek, and percussionist Daniel Saur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6976Norrbotten NEO composer Hilda Paredes.tif (Image-file jib2014_085)
- Composer Hilda Paredes onstage after a performance by Norrbotten NEO members: pianist Märten Landström, violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, and flutist Sara Hammarström at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6977Hilda Paredes.tif (Image-file jib2014_086)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with the ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violist Kim Hellgren (obscured), violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, clarinetist Robert Ek, and percussionists Daniel Saur and Tom Kolor (obscured) in performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6978 Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_087)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with the ensemble Norrbotten NEO: violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violist Kim Hellgren, and violoncellist Elemér Lavotha in performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6979Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_088)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with the ensemble Norrbotten NEO: violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violist Kim Hellgren, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, percussionists Tom Kolor and Daniel Saur, and flutist Sara Hammarström at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6980 Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_089)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood in performance with the ensemble Norrbotten NEO at June in Buffalo 2014 with ensemble members violoncellist Elemér Lavotha and percussionist Daniel Saur in the background, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6981 Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_090)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and conductor Petter Sundkvist performing with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: violist Kim Hellgren, percussionist Daniel Saur, and flutist Sara Hammarström at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6983 Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_091)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and conductor Petter Sundkvist in performance with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violist Kim Hellgren, flutist Sara Hammarström, and percussionists Tom Kolor and Daniel Saur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6984Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_092)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and conductor Petter Sundkvist with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violist Kim Hellgren, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, clarinetist Robert Ek, and percussionists Tom Kolor and Daniel Saur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6986 Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_093)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and composer David Felder onstage with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violist Kim Hellgren, percussionist Tom Kolor, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, and clarinetist Robert Ek after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6991Isherwood David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2014_094)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and composer David Felder onstage with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violist Kim Hellgren, percussionist Tom Kolor, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, and clarinetist Robert Ek after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6992David Felder Isherwood.tif (Image-file jib2014_095)
- Bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and composer David Felder onstage with ensemble Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violist Kim Hellgren, percussionist Tom Kolor, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, and clarinetist Robert Ek after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6995David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2014_096)
- Violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein and violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub from Ensemble Court-Circuit rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_6997 June in Buffalo Ensemble Court-Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_097)
- Pianist Jean-Marie Cottet of Ensemble Court-circuit rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7007Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_098)
- Conductor Julien Leroy and members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: flutist Jérémie Fèvre clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, violist David Rose, and pianist Jean-Marie Cottet rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7008Ensemble Court Circuit rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_099)
- Conductor Julien Leroy conducting at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7014Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_100)
- Conductor Julien Leroy and composer David Felder with members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: flutist Jérémie Fèvre clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violist David Rose, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7024rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_101)
- Conductor Julien Leroy consulting with composer David Felder at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7037David Felder Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_102)
- Composer Joshua Fineberg with pianist Jean-Marie Cottet and clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7043composer Fineberg Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_103)
- Percussionist Eve Payeur rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7049JIB 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_104)
- Conductor Julien Leroy rehearsing members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7051Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_105)
- Conductor Julien Leroy rehearsing members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7052ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_106)
- Composer Bernard Rands giving a lecture to student composers at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7060Bernard Rands lecture.tif (Image-file jib2014_107)
- Bernard Rands giving a lecture at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7061Bernard Rands lecture.tif (Image-file jib2014_108)
- Student composers Binna Kim and Chin Ting Chan with bass-baritone Nicholas Isherwood and composers Stephen Hartke and Bernard Rands at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7063Isherwood Stephen Hartke Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_109)
- Composer Bernard Rands speaking with student composer Binna Kim and two unidentified students at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7073Bernard Rands and students.tif (Image-file jib2014_110)
- Composer Bernard Rands speaking with student composer Binna Kim and two unidentified students at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7074Bernard Rands and students.tif (Image-file jib2014_111)
- Student composers Luciano Leite Barbosa and Mu-Xuan Lin consulting a score at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7082studentcomposers Mu-Xuan-Lin.tif (Image-file jib2014_112)
- Violinist Brusk Zanganeh rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7085JIB 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_113)
- Violinist Brusk Zanganeh rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7087Brusk Zanganeh.tif (Image-file jib2014_114)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist in rehearsal with members of Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, clarinetist Robert Ek, and percussionist Daniel Saur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Norrbotten NEO.tif (Image-file jib2014_115)
- Conductor Petter Sundkvist and composer Mu-Xuan Lin in rehearsal with Norrbotten NEO: pianist Märten Landström, violinist Brusk Zanganeh, violoncellist Elemér Lavotha, flutist Sara Hammarström, clarinetist Robert Ek, and percussionist Daniel Saur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7095Norrbotten NEO and studentcomposer Lin.tif (Image-file jib2014_116)
- Violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein and violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub of Ensemble Court-circuit rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7101Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_117)
- Violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub marking her part at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7102JIB 2014Ingrid Schoenlaub.tif (Image-file jib2014_118)
- Conductor Julien Leroy in performance with Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violist David Rose, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7109Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_119)
- Conductor Julien Leroy onstage after a performance with Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violist David Rose, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7110Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_120)
- Composer David Felder shaking hands with conductor Julien Leroy after a performance by members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violist David Rose, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7112David Felder and Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_121)
- Composer David Felder onstage after a performance by conductor Julien Leroy and members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, and violist David Rose at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7114David Felder.tif (Image-file jib2014_122)
- Ensemble Court-circuit members violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein and violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub acknowledging applause after a performance at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_711 Alexandra Greffin-Klein Ingrid Schoenlaub,cello.tif (Image-file jib2014_123)
- Conductor Julien Leroy in performance with Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: David Felder partial (dist)res(s)toration (2002).tif (Image-file jib2014_124)
- Conductor Julien Leroy shaking hands with composer Joshua Fineberg onstage after a performance with members of Ensemble Court-Circuit: flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Fineberg Objects trouve (2008).tif (Image-file jib2014_125)
- Conductor Julien Leroy in performance with Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7123JIB.tif (Image-file jib2014_126)
- Conductor Julien Leroy acknowledging audience applause after a performance with Ensemble Court-Circuit: pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and percussionist Eve Payeur at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7124JIB Ensemble Court-Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_127)
- Conductor Julien Leroy acknowledging audience applause with Ensemble Court-Circuit: violinist Alexandra Greffin-Klein, pianist Jean-Marie Cottet, clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu, flutist Jérémie Fèvre, percussionist Eve Payeur, and violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7126Ensemble Court-Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_128)
- Ensemble Signal cimbalom player Nick Tolle rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7130June In Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_129)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7133Brad Lubman Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_130)
- Conductor Brad Lubman rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: violist Isabel Hagen, harpist Sophie Rusnock, flutist Kelli Kathman, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7136Ensemble Signal Rehearsal.tif (Image-file jib2014_131)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: cimbalom player Nick Tolle, harpist Sophie Rusnock, percussionist Bill Solomon, violist Isabel Hagen, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, horn player Kate Sheeran, percussionist Carson Moody, and bassist Greg Chudzik at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7138Irving Arditti.tif (Image-file jib2014_132)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, violinist Irvine Arditti, and double bassist Greg Chudzik rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Irving Arditti Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_133)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti examining a score at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7149Brad Lubman Irving Arditti Ensemble Signal.tif (Image-file jib2014_134)
- Ensemble Signal members, harpist Sophie Rusnock, flutist Kelli Kathman, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, and horn player Kate Sheeran rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7150 JIB 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_135)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and violinist Irvine Arditti examining a score at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble Signal Brad Lubman Irving Arditti in Hilda Paredes Senales (2012).tif (Image-file jib2014_136)
- Flutist Jérémie Fèvre, violoncellist Ingrid Schoenlaub, and clarinetist Pierre Dutrieu rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: rehearsal June in Buffalo 2014 Ensemble Court Circuit.tif (Image-file jib2014_137)
- Vocalist Esin Gündüz with violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon and pianist Michael McNeill performing at PAUSA Art House during June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Resaunance Concert at Pausa June 6 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_138)
- Vocalist Esin Gündüz with violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon and pianist Michael McNeill performing at PAUSA Art House during June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Resaunance June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_139)
- Vocalist Esin Gündüz with violoncellist Jonathan Golove, percussionist John Bacon and pianist Michael McNeill performing at PAUSA Art House during June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Resaunance at Pausa June in Buffalo 2014.tif (Image-file jib2014_140)
- Violoncellist Jonathan Golove performing at PAUSA Art House during June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Jonathan Golove.tif (Image-file jib2014_141)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, oboist Jacqueline Leclair, and composer Bernard Rands rehearsing with members of Ensemble Signal: violinists Yuki Numata Resnick and Will Knuth, flutist Kelli Kathman, clarinetist Adrián Sandí, violist Isabel Hagen, and violoncellist Lauren Radnofsky, at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_142)
- Conductor Brad Lubman and oboist Jacqueline Leclair examining a score at rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Brad Lubman conductor Jacqueline Leclar oboe Ensemble Signal Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_143)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, composer Bernard Rands, and conductor Jerry Hou conversing with pianist Oliver Hagen at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Brad Lubman Bernard Rands.tif (Image-file jib2014_144)
- Guitarist Sungmin Shin performing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Sungmin Shin.tif (Image-file jib2014_145)
- Pianist Oliver Hagen performing at June in Buffalo 2014, 2014-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_7199June in Buffalo.tif (Image-file jib2014_146)